The chain usually combines an LLM, large language model, together with a prompt.
链通常将大型语言模型（LLM）与
提示词（Prompt）结合在一起。
And with this building block, you can also put a bunch of these building blocks together to carry out a sequence of operations on your text or on your other data.
有了这个构建模块，你还可以将一堆这
样的构建模块组合在一起，对你的文本
或其他数据按顺序进行操作。
I'm excited to dive into it.
我已经等不及想要深入了解它了。
And then we're also going to load some data that we're going to use.
然后我们还要加载一些即将使用的数据。
So part of the power of these chains is that you can run them over many inputs at a time.
这些链的强大之处在于，它们
可以一次处理多个输入。
Here, we're going to load a Pandas DataFrame.
这里，我们将加载一个Pandas DataFrame。
A Pandas DataFrame is just a data structure that contains a bunch of different elements of data.
Pandas DataFrame只是一个包含许
多不同数据元素的数据结构。
If you're not familiar with Pandas, don't worry about it.
如果你不熟悉Pandas，不用担心。
The main point here is that we're loading some data that we can then use later on.
这里的重点是，我们正在加载一
些数据，稍后将会被用到。
And so if we look inside this Pandas DataFrame, we can see that there is a product column and then a review column.
如果我们查看这个Pandas DataFrame，可
以看到有一个产品列和一个评论列。
And each of these rows is a different data point that we can start passing through our chains.
这些行中的每一行都是一个不同的数据记
录，我们可以开始通过我们的链进行传递。
So the first chain we're going to cover is the LLMChain.
首先我们要介绍的链是LLMChain。
And this is a simple but really powerful chain that underpins a lot of the chains that we'll go over in the future.
这是一个简单但非常强大的链，后
面要介绍的很多链它都能支持。
And so we're going to import three different things.
我们将导入三个不同的库。
We're going to import the OpenAI model, so the LLM.
我们将导入OpenAI模型，即LLM。
And then we're going to import the LLMChain.
然后我们将导入LLMChain。
And so first, what we're going to do is we're going to initialize the language model that we want to use.
首先，我们要初始化我们
想要使用的语言模型。
So we're going to initialize the ChatOpenAI with a high temperature so that we can get some fun descriptions.
我们将用一个比较高的
temperature值来初始化
ChatOpenAI，这样能获得一些有意
思的结果。
Now we're going to initialize a prompt, and this prompt is going to take in a variable called product.
现在我们要初始化一个提示词模
板，这个提示词模板将接收一个名
为产品（product）的变量。
It's going to ask the LLM to generate what the best name is to describe a company that makes that product.
它会要求LLM根据产品名称，为制作该产品
的公司取一个最佳的公司描述名称。
And then finally, we're going to combine these two things into a chain.
最后，我们将这两者结合成一条链。
And so this is what we call an LLMChain, and it's quite simple.
这就是我们所说的LLMChain，非常简单。
But now this chain will let us run through the prompt and into the LLM in a sequential manner.
这条链将提示词模板和
LLM按顺序连接起来。
And so if we have a product called "Queen Size Sheet Set", we can run this through the chain by using "chain.run".
如果我们有一个名为“双人床床单套
装”的产品，我们可以通过使用“chain
.run”将它传入链，并运行链。
And what    will do is it will format the prompt under the hood, and then it will pass the whole prompt into the LLM.
它会在后台格式化提示词，然后将
格式化后的提示词传给LLM。
And so we can see that we get back the name of this hypothetical company called "Royal Beddings".
我们可以看到LLM给这个生产床单的
公司取了个名字叫做"皇家寝具"。
so here would be a good time to pause, and you can input any product descriptions that you would want, and you can see what the chain will output as a result.
建议你暂停视频，去Notebook输入你想要
的产品描述，看看这条链会输出什么结果。
So the LLMChain is the most basic type of chain, and that's going to be used a lot in the future.
LLMChain是最基本的链类
型，以后经常会被用到。
And so we can see how this will be used in the next type of chain, which will be "Sequential Chains".
我们来看看下一种常用的链，也就是"
顺序链（Sequential Chains）"。
And so Sequential Chains run a sequence of chains one after another.
顺序链是将一系列链一个接一个地运行。
So to start, you're going to import the SimpleSequentialChain.
首先，你需要导入
SimpleSequentialChain。
And so here we're going to first create one chain, which uses an LLM and a prompt.
这里我们首先创建一条链，它
使用LLM和提示词模板。
And this prompt is going to take in the product and will return the best name to describe that company.
这个提示词模板将接受输入一个产品参数
，并返回最佳的产品所属公司描述名称。
So that will be the first chain.
那将是第一条链。
Then we're going to create a second chain.
然后我们要创建第二条链。
And the second chain will take in the company name and then output a 20 word description of that company.
第二条链会接收公司名称，然后
输出一个20字的公司描述。
And so you can imagine how these chains might want to be run one after another,
你可以想象这些链需要
一条接一条地运行，
We can easily do this by creating a SimpleSequentialChain where we have the two chains described there.
通过创建一个
SimpleSequentialChain我们可以很
容易的实现这一点，参数中包含了两
条链的描述。
And we'll call this overall_simple_chain.
我们将这条链命名为
overall_simple_chain。
Now, what you can do is run this chain over any product description.
现在，你可以在任何产品
描述上运行这条链。
And so if we use it with the product above the "Queen Size Sheet Set",
我们可以用之前的“双人
床床单套装”来测试，
we can run it over and we can see that at first outputs "Royal Bedding",
让我们运行它看看，先是
输出了“皇家寝具”，
and then it passes it into the second chain and it comes up with this description of what that company could be about.
然后将它传递到第二条链，得
出关于该公司可能的描述。
The simple sequential chain(SimpleSequentialChain) works well when there's only a single input and a single output.
简单顺序链（SimpleSequentialChain）在
只有一个输入和一个输出时表现非常好。
But what about when there are multiple inputs or multiple outputs?
但是当有多个输入或多
个输出时该怎么办？
And so we can do this by using just the regular SequentialChain.
我们可以通过使用常规的
SequentialChain来实现这一点。
And then you're going to create a bunch of chains that we're going to use one after another.
然后你可以创建一系列链，后
面我们将依次调用这些链。
We're going to be using the data from above, which has a review.
我们将使用上面的数据，
其中包含一篇评论。
And so the first chain, we're going to take the review and translate it into English.
首先，我们将用第一条链
将评论翻译成英语。
With a second chain, we're going to create a summary of that review in one sentence.
然后用第二条链，我们将用
一句话总结这篇评论。
And this will use the previously generated English review.
这里用的是之前生成的英语评论。
The third chain is going to detect what the language of the review was in the first place.
第三条链将检测评论最初
是用什么语言写的。
And so if you notice, this is using the review variable that is coming from the original review.
注意看，这里使用的是"Review
"变量，表示原始的评论。
And finally, the fourth chain will take in multiple inputs.
最后，第四条链将接收多个输入。
So this will take in the summary variable, which we calculated with the second chain and the language variable, which we calculated with the third chain.
它将接收我们用第二条链得到的摘
要"summary"变量和我们用第三条链
得到的语言"language"变量。
And it's going to ask for a follow up response to the summary in the specified language.
要求后续对摘要回复时，使用指定的语言。
One important thing to note about all these sub chains is that the input keys and output keys need to be pretty precise.
关于所有这些子链，需要注意的是输入名
和输出名需要非常精确，这非常重要。
So here we're taking in review.
所以这里我们接收"Review"。
This is a variable that will be passed in at the start.
这是一个在开始时传入的变量。
We can see that we explicitly set the output key to English review.
我们可以看到我们明确设置了输
出名为"English_Review"。
This is then used in the next prompt down below, where we take in English review with that same variable name.
这在下面的下一个提示中使用，我们用相
同的变量名接收"English_Review"。
And we set the output key of that chain to summary, which we can see is used in the final chain.
我们将该链的输出名设置为"summary"，我
们可以看到它在最后一条链中使用。
The third prompt takes in review, the original variable and output language, which is again used in the final prompt.
第三个提示词模板接收原始的"Review
"变量和输出"language"，这些在最后
的提示词模板中会被再次使用。
And if you get any key errors, you should definitely check that they are lined up.
如果出现任何关键性的错误，一
定要检查变量名是否一致。
So the Simple Sequential Chain takes in multiple chains, where each one has a single input and a single output.
简单顺序链（Simple
Sequential Chain）接收多条链
，每条链都有一个输入和一个输
出。
To see a visual representation of this, we can look at the slide where it has one chain feeding into the other chain, one after another.
一图胜千言，可以看这张幻灯片
的图示，一条链的输出传入另一
条链作为输入，一个接一个。
Here we can see a visual description of the sequential chain, comparing it to the above chain.
在这里，我们可以看到顺序链（
Sequential Chain）的图示，并把它
跟前面的简单顺序链进行比较。
You can notice that any step in the chain can take in multiple input variables.
你会注意到链中的任何步骤都
可以接收多个输入变量。
This is useful when you have more complicated downstream chains that need to be a composition of multiple previous chains.
当你有复杂的下游链需要和多个
上游链组合，这会非常有用。
Now that we have all these chains, we can easily combine them in the SequentialChain.
有了所有这些链之后，我们可以轻松地将
它们组合在顺序链（SequentialChain）中。
So you'll notice here that we'll pass in the four chains we created into the chains variable.
首先，我们将创建的四条链作
为数组保存到chains变量。
We'll create the inputs variable with the one human input, which is the review.
我们用一个人类输入也就是"Review
"来创建"inputs_variables"。
And then we want to return all of the intermediate outputs.
然后我们想返回所有中间输出：
So the English review, the summary, and then the follow-up message.
"English_Review"、"summary"，
然后是"followup_message"。
Now we can run this over some of the data.
现在我们可以传一些数据来运行试试。
So let's choose a review and pass it in through the overall chain.
让我们选择一条评论并传递给整条链。
We can see here that the original review looks like it was in French.
我们可以看到原始的"
Review"似乎是法语的。
We can see the English review as a translation.
我们可以看到"
English_Review"作为翻
译。
We can see a summary of that review, and then we can see a follow-up message in the original language of French.
我们可以看到评论的"summary"，然后我们
可以看到法语的"followup_message"。
So far we've covered the LLMChain and then a Sequential Chain.
到目前为止，我们已经介绍了
LLMChain和顺序链（Sequential
Chain）。
But what if you want to do something more complicated?
但是，如果你想完成更复杂的任务呢？
A pretty common but basic operation is to route an input to a chain, depending on what exactly that input is.
一个相当常见的基本操作是，根据输入
内容路由到某条链来处理你的输入。
A good way to imagine this is if you have multiple subchains, each of which specialized for a particular type of input, you could have a Router Chain,
可以想象以下，如果你有多条子链，
每条子链专门负责处理某种特定类
型的输入，这种情况下你可以使用
路由链（Router Chain），
For a concrete example, let's look at where we are routing between different types of chains, depending on the subject that seems to come in.
举一个具体的例子来看看我们如何根据
输入的内容来路由到不同类型的链。
So we have here different prompts.
这里我们有不同的提示词。
One prompt is good for answering physics questions.
一个提示词适合回答物理问题。
The second prompt is good for answering math questions, the third for history, and then a fourth for computer science.
第二个提示词适合回答数学问题
，第三个提示词适合历史，第四个
提示词适合计算机科学。
Let's define all these prompt templates.
让我们定义所有这些提示词模板。
After we have these prompt templates, we can then provide more information about them.
有了这些提示模板后，我们可以
提供更多关于它们的信息。
This description for the physics one is good for answering questions about physics.
这个物理模板的描述非常
适合回答物理问题。
This information is going to be passed to the router chain, so the router chain can decide when to use this subchain.
这些信息将传递给路由链，路由链会根据
这些信息来决定什么时候该使用哪条子链。
Let's now import the other types of chains that we need.
现在让我们导入其他需要的链类型。
Here we need a MultiPromptChain.
这里我们需要用MultiPromptChain，
As you can see, all the options we have are prompt templates themselves, but this is just one type of thing that you can route between.
如你所见，我们所有的选项都是提示模板，
但实际上不止是可以路由这一种类型，
You can route between any type of chain.
除此之外你也可以在任何其
他类型的链之间路由。
The other classes that we'll import here are an LLMRouterChain.
这里还需要引用LLMRouterChain。
This uses a language model itself to route between the different subchains.
这个程序借助大语言模型的帮
助在不同的子链之间路由。
This is where the description and the name provided above will be used.
这就是为什么上面需要提供名称和描述，
语言模型根据这些信息判断如何路由。
Now we can get around to using it.
现在我们可以开始使用它了。
We now create the destination chains.
接下来创建目标链，
As you can see, each destination chain itself is a language model chain, an LLMChain.
如你所见，每个目标链本身就是一
个语言模型链，即LLMChain。
In addition to the destination chains, we also need a default chain.
除了目标链，我们还需要一个默认链。
This is a chain that's called when the router can't decide which of the subchains to use.
默认链是在路由找不到合适的子链
调用时，用来备用的一条链路。
And the example above, this might be called when the input question has nothing to do with physics, math, history, or computer science.
在上面的例子中，当输入问题与
物理、数学、历史或计算机科学无
关时，就会调用这条链路。
Now we define the template that is used by the LLM to route between the different chains.
现在我们定义一个路由的提示词模板，让
LLM根据提示词的内容在不同链之间路由。
This has instructions of the task to be done, as well as the specific formatting that the output should be in.
这里包含了完成任务的说明，
以及输出内容的的格式。
Let's put a few of these pieces together to build the router chain.
让我们把这些部分组合起来，构建路由链。
First, we create the full router template by formatting it with the destinations that we defined above.
首先，我们通过使用上面定义的
目标来创建完整的路由模板。
This template is flexible to a bunch of different types of destinations.
这个模板适用于许多不同类型的目标。
One thing you can do here is pause and add different types of destinations.
建议你在这里暂停，然后尝
试添加不同类型的目标。
So up here, rather than just physics, math, history, and computer science, you could add a different subject like English or Latin.
在这里，除了物理、数学、历史和
计算机科学，你还可以添加其他
学科，如英语或拉丁语。
This is important as it will help this chain decide which subchains to route between.
这很重要，因为它会帮助决定这
条链在哪些子链之间路由。
And finally, putting it all together, we can create the overall chain.
最后，把所有内容放在一起，
我们可以创建整条链。
It has destination chains, which we pass in here.
它有目标链，我们在这里传入。
And then we also pass in the default chain.
然后传入默认链，
We can now use this chain.
现在可以使用这条链了。
So let's ask it some questions.
让我们向它提问试试。
If we ask it a question about physics, we should hopefully see that it is routed to the physics chain with the input, "What is black body radiation?",
如果我们问一个关于物理的问题，
希望能看到它被路由到物理链，输
入是“什么是黑体辐射？”
and then that is passed into the chain down below.
然后这个问题会传到下面的链。
And we can see that the response is very detailed with lots of physics details.
可以看到回复非常详细，
包含了很多物理细节。
You should pause the video here and try putting in different inputs.
建议你在这里暂停视频，自己
尝试输入不同的内容试试。
You can try with all the other types of special chains that we have defined above.
可以尝试我们之前定义的
路由链中的其他链。
So for example, if we ask it a math question,
比如，如果问一个数学问题，
we should see that it's routed to the math chain and then passed into that.
应该看到它被路由到数学链，
然后把问题传入数学链。
We can also see what happens when we pass in a question that is not related to any of the subchains.
还可以试试当我们提出一个与这些子
链都无关的问题时会发生什么。
So here we ask it a question about biology and we can see the chain that it chooses is "None".
这里我们问一个关于生物学的问题
，可以看到它选择的链是“无”。
This means that it will be passed to the default chain, which itself is just a generic call to the language model.
这意味着问题会被传递到默认链，也就是
直接当做一个通用问题去问语言模型。
The language model luckily knows a lot about biology, so it can help us out here.
幸运的是，语言模型对了解很多
生物学知识，所以它还是可以帮
助我们回答这个问题。
Now that we've covered these basic building blocks types of chains, we can start to put them together to create really interesting applications.
现在我们已经学习了这些基本的构
建块类型的链，我们可以尝试将它们
组合在一起，创建有趣的应用。
For example, in the next section, we're going to cover how to create a chain that can do question answering over your documents.
在下一节课程中，我们将介绍如何创
建一个可以基于文档问答的链。